<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Auto Silent</string>
    <string name="sunday_code">1</string>
    <string name="monday_code">2</string>
    <string name="tuesday_code">3</string>
    <string name="wednesday_code">4</string>
    <string name="thursday_code">5</string>
    <string name="friday_code">6</string>
    <string name="saturday_code">7</string>
    <string name="silent_mode">0</string>
    <string name="vibrate_mode">1</string>
    <string name="ringer_mode">2</string>
    <string name="setScheduleHelpContent">Select the days you want recurring alarms via checkbox.
    From time is the time when phone should activate vibrate mode, To time is the time when the phone will
    be back to Normal mode.</string>
    <string name="viewScheduleHelpContent">Here you can view your saved schedules. Select the schedule
        and you can explore more options like deactivating, modifying or deleting that schedule.</string>
    <string name="oneTimeHelpContent">Here you can set a non-recurring one time only schedule easily and conveniently. In one time schedule,
        you can choose the mode i.e. Silent or vibrate. The phone will automatically activate your selected mode at the From time
        and turn back to normal mode at To time. Currently the app
    supports only Single one time schedule. More one-time schedules will be supported in future updates.</string>
    <string name="oneTimeHelpCancel">To cancel, again select one time schedule and you can see your preset one time details are available there.
    Also, there is an extra cancel button if you have a one time non-recurring schedule set. Just press the cancel button to cancel your
     one time schedule.</string>
    <string name="helpFeedback">Report bug or provide feedback? Reach me at mithunjmistry@gmail.com. Constructive feedbacks and ideas are
    always appreciated.</string>
    <string name="setRestartContent">We know that you restart your phone to optimize it and make it run better. So, the app will
    deactivate all your schedules automatically for you. You can simply open your schedule and activate it again.</string>
</resources>
